# **DMITRY STARKOV**

Moscow, Russia



starkdev@icloud.com



linkedin.com/in/starkdev

### **Summary**

I'm 24 years old. Graduated from professional college. Studied at CVUT in Prague. Travelling through Europe. Living in Prague and Moscow. Fast learning programmer for more than 9 years. Last 3 years I'm working on Mobile Development. Registered in Apple and Goolge developer programs.

All languages, skills and technologies mentioned below not only studied, but also applied in practice. My Applications are covered by Unit and UI Tests, Fastlane used for Continious Integration and Git as Version Control System. I always interested in learning new languages and technologies like TensorFlow, AR or GraphQL and applying it in mobile or desktop applications I developing.

Programming languages with professional knowledge:

- Swift (3+ years)
- Python (2+ years)
- Dart (1+ years)
- C (2 years)
- C++ (2 years)
- C# (2+ years)
- Javascript (1 year)
- NodeJS (1 year)
- Visual Basic (1 year)
- Delphi (1 year)
- Bash (6 month)

Skills and Knowledges: iOS Applications, Desktop Applications, Crossplatform Applications, Web Services, Progressive Web Applications, Chat Bots, Data Mining, Web Scraping, Application Security, In-App Purchases, Advertising, Analytics, Big Data, AI, Machine Learning, NLP, AR, Cryptocurrencies, Cryptography, SQL, GraphQL, NoSQL, Network Interception, Data Mockup, Automate Testing, Automate Screenshots, Lottie Animations, Json Web Tokens, Realm, Core Data, Combine Framework, Alamofire, Swift Package Manager, CocoaPods, SwiftUI, UIKit, WPF, XAML, HTML, JSON, XML, CSV, Regular Expressions, Dio, Hive, GetX, Provider.

Technologies and Tools: Flutter, Xcode, VS Code, Visual Studio, Git, Fastlane, Firebase, Parse Server, Cisco, Microsoft SQL Server, Oracle Database, PostgreSQL, MongoDB, TensorFlow, Blockchain, Wolfram Mathematica, Google App Engine, Microsoft Azure, Amazon Web Services, Google AdMob, .Net, Selenium, Xamarin, React Native, Postman.

Communication: Conversational English (B1), Native Russian (C2) and Fluent Czech (B2).

### **Experience**



#### **Mobile Application Developer**

Self-employed

Feb 2018 - Present (3 years 3 months +)

Developing Mobile Applications for App Store and Google Play. iOS Applications using Swift and SwiftUI. Cross-platform Applications using Flutter.

## Python Developer

Self-employed

Aug 2016 - Jan 2018 (1 year 6 months)

Server-Side Applications, Chat Bots, Automate Cryptocurrency Trading, Machine Learning Models, NLP and Computer Vision using Python Language.

### **Education**



## **Faculty of Information Technology CTU in Prague**

2018 - 2019



### Programming College

2012 - 2016

### **Skills**

Research • User Experience (UX) • Continuous Integration • Project Planning • Testing • iOS Development • AI • Machine Learning • Flutter • GraphQL